{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Chapter10_Grammer.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "Gli piace leggere.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1461001445.2102537,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They like reading.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "I don't like love stories.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1461001337.9642189,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Non mi piacciono le storie d'amore.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Gli piace la musica pop.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1461001475.5975945,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He likes pop music.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all like dancing.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1461001437.7550795,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Vi piace ballare.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "He likes pop music.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1461001459.6221223,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Gli piace la musica pop.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "They like contemporary novels.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1461001306.0886638,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Gli piacciono i rmanzi contemporanei.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all like Latin American dancing.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1461001504.108801,
            "question": "Given the definition \"piacciono i balli latinoamericani.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "We don't like expensive hotels.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1461001372.2679684,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Non ci piacciono gli alberghi costosi.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Non ci piacciono gli alberghi costosi.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We don't like expensive hotels.\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Mi piace il cinema.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1461001522.8447213,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I like the movies.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "You like the theater.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ti piace il teatro.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "You (formal) don't like classical music concerts.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Non Le piacciono i concerti di musica classica.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Non Le piacciono i concerti di musica classica.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You (formal) don't like classical music concerts.\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Ti piace il teatro.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You like the theater.\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Non mi piacciono le storie d'amore.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1461001963.9283574,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I don't like love stories.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "piacciono i balli latinoamericani.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all like Latin American dancing.\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "We like traveling.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Ci piace viaggiare.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Ci piace viaggiare.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We like traveling.\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "I like the movies.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Mi piace il cinema.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Vi piace ballare.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all like dancing.\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "She likes British bands.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Le piacciono i gruppi inglesi.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Le piacciono i gruppi inglesi.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"She likes British bands.\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Gli piacciono i rmanzi contemporanei.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They like contemporary novels.\"?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "They like reading.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Gli piace leggere.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 0
        }
    ]
}